<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Depression on Nicholas C. Jacobson</title>
    <link>http://www.nicholasjacobson.com/tags/depression/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Depression on Nicholas C. Jacobson</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 21:13:14 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.nicholasjacobson.com/tags/depression/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Phenotyping Mood Disorders Reproducible R Code</title>
      <link>http://www.nicholasjacobson.com/post/digital_biomarkers_mood_disorders/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicholasjacobson.com/post/digital_biomarkers_mood_disorders/</guid>
      <description>OverviewThis post documents reproducible code accompanying the manuscript draft “Digital Biomarkers of Mood Disorders and Symptom Change” by Nicholas C. Jacobson, Hilary M. Weingardenm and Sabine Wilhelm (published in Nature Partner Journal (npj): Digital Medicine). This code uses machine learning to predict the diagnostic status and depressive symptom change in a a group of 23 patients with bipolar disorder or major depressive disorder and 32 non-disordered controls using actigraphy data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mood Triggers</title>
      <link>http://www.nicholasjacobson.com/project/mood-triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.nicholasjacobson.com/project/mood-triggers/</guid>
      <description>Mood Triggers is an Android App released on the Google Play Store.
Link to Mood Triggers App on the Google Play Store
Youtube video of Mood Triggers
Mood Triggers will help you identify things that can trigger your anxious and depressed moods for FREE.
Features of Mood Triggers: Mood Triggers can help you keep a diary of: 1. Your anxiety and depression in your daily life 2. Health behaviors including your heart rate, number of steps, and sleep duration (all collected by the app)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>